Constitution Amendment 22 Two terms maximum, that's all you can do Power-hungry minds won't always touch true A loophole in the system to break through
History repeats the dictatorial dreams FDR's legacy led these safeguard schemes Now another man claims exceptional means To circumvent what democracy means The framers saw this coming Chess and balance is eroding When ambition meets delusion Democracy imploding
Constitution, Amendment 22.
Two terms maximum, that's all you can do.
Power-hungry minds won't always trust through a loophole in the system.
It's a breakthrough.
Breakthrough.
Trying to breakthrough.